#### **Personal Profile**

Junior at Virginia Tech majoring in Computer Science with a Minor in Human Computer Interaction. Passionate about programming. Work experience with Django and React. Currently focused on web development. Wants to learn more about UX design. Personable and gets along with peers. Always learning more and pursuing multiple interests.

# **Experience**

## Internship at Ubisoft (05/2019 - 08/2019)

Customer support agent dealing with fraud detection, account verification, and computer compatibility issues. Utilized Salesforce tools.

## Black Falcons (Ubuntu and Cisco Packet Tracer Specialist, 05/2018 - 05/2020)

Cyber Patriots club hosted by the Airforce. Deals with cybersecurity and advanced IT work. Was a team lead. Team's Ubuntu and Packet Tracer Networking expert. Placed 2nd at state level.

## Exelaration Software Engineer Intern (09/2021 - 08/2022)

Working as a consultant for <u>Rhythm</u>'s Customer Support portal. Utilizing Django REST API, React, Typescript, and Docker to perform end-to-end modifications on an existing support system and increase customer support effectiveness.

#### **Education**

# Undergraduate at Virginia Tech (08/2020 - Current)

Class of 2024. Computer Science Major. Human Computer Interaction Minor.

**Cisco Networking Academy Packet Tracer (2019)** 

In-depth configuration of LAN networks.

**Unity Envision course at George Mason University (07/2018)** 

Course on Game Design, Unity, and C#.

#### **Skills**

#### Languages

C#, C, Python, Java, and JavaScript.

**Tools and Frameworks** 

Unity, Blender, Git, Django, React, and Docker.

#### **Activities**

The Gaming Project (2014 - 2020)

A game development club.

**Intramural Pickleball (2022 - current)**